https://www.gamo.com/en/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentDiscover our 10X Quick Shot unique technology. Already available at your local dealer.
You're in:
Cart
Air Rifles1000 FPSFIXED BARRELYoung10X MULTISHOTPCPGAMO POWERAir PistolsPRE-CHARGED PNEUMATIC PISTOLSBREAK BARREL PISTOLSCO2 PISTOLSPelletsCOMPETITIONCountryTRAININGMultishotPCPPERFORMANCEPISTOL PELLETSHEAVY PELLETSOpticsPERFORMANCE OPTICSAccessoriesGUN COVERSCLEANING AND MANTEINANCEHUNTING AND SHOOTINGOTHER ACCESSORIESTARGETSOutdoor EquipmentBACKPACKSJACKETSOTHER ACCESSORIESPANTSBOOTSFLEECE JACKETSPOLAR FLEECESPOLOSSHIRTSSWEATERST-SHIRTSVESTSAbout GAMOGamo TechnologyIconic BrandsOur DNADistributorsPro Shot IDCustomer supportFAQ’sContactTerminology
MenuAir Rifles1000 FPSFIXED BARRELYoung10X MULTISHOTPCPGAMO POWERAir PistolsPRE-CHARGED PNEUMATIC PISTOLSBREAK BARREL PISTOLSCO2 PISTOLSPelletsCOMPETITIONCountryTRAININGMultishotPCPPERFORMANCEPISTOL PELLETSHEAVY PELLETSOpticsPERFORMANCE OPTICSAccessoriesGUN COVERSCLEANING AND MANTEINANCEHUNTING AND SHOOTINGOTHER ACCESSORIESTARGETSOutdoor EquipmentBACKPACKSJACKETSOTHER ACCESSORIESPANTSBOOTSFLEECE JACKETSPOLAR FLEECESPOLOSSHIRTSSWEATERST-SHIRTSVESTSAbout GAMOGamo TechnologyIconic BrandsOur DNADistributorsPro Shot IDCustomer supportFAQ’sContactTerminology
Air Rifles1000 FPSFIXED BARRELYoung10X MULTISHOTPCPGAMO POWERAir PistolsPRE-CHARGED PNEUMATIC PISTOLSBREAK BARREL PISTOLSCO2 PISTOLSPelletsCOMPETITIONCountryTRAININGMultishotPCPPERFORMANCEPISTOL PELLETSHEAVY PELLETSOpticsPERFORMANCE OPTICSAccessoriesGUN COVERSCLEANING AND MANTEINANCEHUNTING AND SHOOTINGOTHER ACCESSORIESTARGETSOutdoor EquipmentBACKPACKSJACKETSOTHER ACCESSORIESPANTSBOOTSFLEECE JACKETSPOLAR FLEECESPOLOSSHIRTSSWEATERST-SHIRTSVESTSAbout GAMOGamo TechnologyIconic BrandsOur DNADistributorsPro Shot IDCustomer supportFAQ’sContactTerminology
MenuAir Rifles1000 FPSFIXED BARRELYoung10X MULTISHOTPCPGAMO POWERAir PistolsPRE-CHARGED PNEUMATIC PISTOLSBREAK BARREL PISTOLSCO2 PISTOLSPelletsCOMPETITIONCountryTRAININGMultishotPCPPERFORMANCEPISTOL PELLETSHEAVY PELLETSOpticsPERFORMANCE OPTICSAccessoriesGUN COVERSCLEANING AND MANTEINANCEHUNTING AND SHOOTINGOTHER ACCESSORIESTARGETSOutdoor EquipmentBACKPACKSJACKETSOTHER ACCESSORIESPANTSBOOTSFLEECE JACKETSPOLAR FLEECESPOLOSSHIRTSSWEATERST-SHIRTSVESTSAbout GAMOGamo TechnologyIconic BrandsOur DNADistributorsPro Shot IDCustomer supportFAQ’sContactTerminology
Search
Close
0,00€
Cart
Privacy policyConfidentiality and security are core values of GAMO OUTDOOR, S.L.U. and we therefore undertake to ensure the User’s privacy at all times and not to gather any unnecessary information. Below we provide all the information necessary regarding our Privacy Policy in relation to the personal data collected, explaining:Who is the processor of your data.The purpose for which we gather the data requested.What are the legal grounds for their processing.The length of time we store the data.Who your data are disclosed to.What your rights are.Data Controller:GAMO OUTDOOR, S.L.U. (B85225282)Carretera Santa Creu de Calafell, nº 43Sant Boi de Llobregat (Barcelona)gamo@gamo.comPurposes, legal grounds and storage of the processing of data sent via the:CONTACT FORM.Purpose: To provide the means for contacting us and for answering your requests for information and also to send you information on our products, services and activities including via digital means if you check the acceptance box.Legal grounds: The user’s consent when requesting information via our contact form and checking the acceptance box for the sending of information.Storage: Until your request has been resolved via our form or answered by email, if no new processing has been generated. In the case of accepting commercial information, until you cancel your subscription.REGISTRATION FORM.Purpose: To record you as a registered user, grant you access to the exclusive contents and services for registered users and to send you information and offers on our products and services including via electronic means.Legal grounds: Consent of the user and legitimate interest in informing our clients and registered users regarding our products and services.Storage: Until the registered user requests de-registration and subsequently during the legally provided time periods.SENDING OF EMAILS.Purpose: To answer your information requests, deal with your requests and answer any inquiries or doubts.   Legal grounds: The user’s consent when requesting information via our email address.Storage: Once your email request has been answered, if no new processing has been generated.Obligation to provide your personal data and the consequences for a failure to do so.The supply of personal data requires a minimum age of 14 years, or, if applicable, sufficient legal capacity to enter into a contract.The personal data requested are necessary to manage your requests and/or render the services that can be contracted and therefore any failure to do so signifies we cannot attend to you correctly nor provide the service requested.Recipients of the dataYour data are confidential and will not be transferred to third parties unless legally required.Rights in relation to your personal dataAny person may withdraw their consent at any time after granting it for the processing of their data. Under no circumstance does withdrawal of consent affect the execution of the subscription contract or the relations established previously.Likewise, you may also exercise the following rights:Request access to your personal data or rectification of same when inaccurate.Request their erasure when, amongst other reasons, they are no longer necessary for the purpose for which they were gathered.Request restriction of processing in certain circumstances.Request objection to the processing of your data due to your particular situation.Request data portability when so provided in law.Other rights recognised in applicable law.Where and how to exercise your Rights: By writing to the party concerned at their postal or electronic address (provided in section A), indicating the reference “Personal Data”, specifying the right to be exercised and with regard to which personal data.In the event of any dispute with the company with regard to the processing of your data, you may lodge a claim with the Data Protection Authority (www.agpd.es).CookiesThis webpage uses only its own and third-party (Google Analytics) technical, personalisation and analysis cookies which under no circumstance process personal data nor capture browsing habits for advertising purposes.As a result, pursuant to article 22 of the Law on Information Society Services, and given that analysis cookies are used, we have requested your authorisation to use them and informed you of same, and they will be installed after a reasonable period of time for the user to have time to decide whether or not to authorise them.Security of your personal dataIn order to safeguard the security of your personal data, we inform you that we  have adopted all the necessary measures of a technical and organisational nature to ensure the security of your personal data against alteration, loss and non-authorised processing and access.Updating your dataIt is important you inform us whenever there has been any modification so we may update your personal data; otherwise we cannot be liable for the accuracy of same.We shall not be liable for the privacy policy regarding the personal data you may supply to third parties via the links on our webpage.This privacy policy may be modified to adapt them to any changes on our website together with any legal or jurisprudential modifications regarding personal data which may appear, and you are therefore requested to read this policy every time you supply your data via this Website.© 2020 GAMO. All rights reserved.
